SWATHI NATARAJAN

Address: Somerest, NJ 08873 Phone: 732-599-9325 Email: Swathi.ashwin@icloud.com

SUMMARY

Reliable and professional with 3 years of functional experience in providing critical, administrative and financial services. Top-notch computer and financial software skills. Talents in payroll administration and invoice lodging. Detailed account specialist recognized for successfully batching, posting and matching over 50 invoices daily.

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

Vendor Communication | Internal Auditing | Vendor Account monitoring | Cheque processing | Account Analysis | Bill Payment | SAP | Data entry | Clerical abilities | Accounting Mastery | Invoicing and billing | Account reconciliation | Financial statement preparation | Accounting operations management | Quicken expertise

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts: Accounting and Computer science from VIT University, India

04/2011

EXPERIENCE

Billing Specialist – 01/2022 to Present Lens Depot, NJ

- Send invoices and account updates to clients
- Keep an accurate record of client accounts and outstanding balances
- Tracking and resolving payment issues
- Validate debit accounts to ensure the credibility of payments
- Issue receipts for received payments.
- Address and solve client questions and issues
- Securely handle client data and payment information.
- Provide regular and accurate reports to billing data

HR Intern – 06/2021 to 12/2021

Technology Square, Piscataway, NJ

- Performing HR administrative duties such as email correspondence, filing, record keeping,
- Learning & Development
- Assisting with open enrollment project planning and communication
- Other admin activities such as vendor communication, coordinating for the payments
- Prepare/Manage Ad-hoc reporting requests
- Reviews and prepare documents, presentation, and/or report as requested

Accounting Specialist - 03/2017 to 02/2020 Hexacorp LLC, Somerest, NJ

- Accounts payable and receivable check
- Posted receipts to appropriate general ledger account
- Monitored payments due from clients and promptly contacted with past due payments
- Reconciled discrepancies between accounts receivable and general ledger account
- Researched and resolved accounts payable discrepancies
- Supervised invoice processing, purchase orders, expense report, client memos and payment transactions.
- Performed accounts receivable duties including invoicing, researching chargebacks, discrepancies and reconciliations.
- Managed and responded to all correspondence and inquiries from vendors and clients
- Communicated with customers to identify and resolve outstanding payments

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Technical Skills: MS-Office

ERP Knowledge: SAP, Quickbooks, ADP, Citrix, APX, Tally 9.0